Finding aid for the Aldous and Laura Huxley papers, 1925-2007 LSC.2009
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Aldous Huxley Papers
  - Lectures and Speeches
    - Recordings
      - label reads: "Aldous Big Sur Tape? [crossed out] UCSB lecture series ?", no date; UCLA Tape No. 442; not digitized
      - Label reads: "Time Must have a Stop Aldous Huxley Readings from Recorded 1949 Los Angeles" [re-issued by Big Sur Tapes 1972], UCLA Tape No. 433; not digitized
      - Label reads: "The Population Explosion Aldous Huxley The Human Situation Series 62 Recorded Live 1959 Santa Barbara" [re-issued by Big Sur Tapes 1972], 1962; UCLA Tape No. 434; not digitized
      - Laura Huxley, unidentified speaking event, [discussing states of consciousness ?]; Label reads: About Rage, "Dilusion", no date; UCLA Tape No. 12; Note on tape: Side one: "Discussion About Rage", Side two: "Nothing." Note on cassette tape: "Dilusion." (Box 85, Folder 1)
      - Aldous Huxley, discussion with faculty of Lake Forest College, Lake Forest, Ill., 1960 Apr 8; UCLA Tape No. 107A; See 107 (Box 91, Folder 1)
      - 107A: Aldous Huxley, discussion with faculty of Lake Forest College, Lake Forest, Ill. 107B: Aldous Huxley, interview, Mike Wallace, "Democracy Today & Tomorrow," ABC-TV., 1960 Apr 8 and 1958 May 18; UCLA Tape No. 107; Side 2: monaural@ 3-3/4 ips, 30 min in each Sullivan's H-1 & 4. Note on box: Side 1 - all of tape, but last 10 minutes omitted; poor quality. Original owned by Lake Forest College, from Sullivan's H-3. Side 2: Segment A - 30 minutes interivew with AH by Mike Wallace on ABC-TV, 18 May 1958, "Democracy Today & Tomorrow", Sullivan's H-1. Side 2: Segment B - 30 minutes, MIT Science Reporter: AH on Image and Reality" from NET-TV, Sullivan's H-4. With yellow post-it note: "What is a proper education for freedom." (Box 91, Folder 14)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, "The future is in our hands", 1959 Apr 27; UCLA Tape No. 108; 3-3/4 ips, full track. Lecture 9. (Box 92, Folder 1)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Integrate education (original tape damaged), 1959 Feb 9; UCLA Tape No. 110; 3-3/4 ips, full track. Lecture 1. (Box 92, Folder 3)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Man and his planet, 1959 Feb 16; UCLA Tape No. 111; 3-3/4 ips, full track. Lecture 2. (Box 92, Folder 4)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, More nature in art, 1959 Mar 2; UCLA Tape No. 112; 3-3/4 ips, full track. Lecture 3. (Box 92, Folder 5)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Population Explosion (The), Part I, 1959 Mar 9; UCLA Tape No. 113; 3-3/4 ips, full track. Lecture 4, Part I of II. (Box 92, Folder 6)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Population Explosion (The), Part II, 1959 Mar 9; UCLA Tape No. 114; 3-3/4 ips, full track. Lecture 4, Part II of II. (Box 92, Folder 7)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, How original is original sin, Part I, 1959 Mar 16; UCLA Tape No. 115; 3-3/4 ips, full track. Lecture 5, Part I of II. (Box 92, Folder 8)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, How original is original sin, Part II, 1959 Mar 16; UCLA Tape No. 116; 3-3/4 ips, full track. Lecture 5, Part II of II. (Box 92, Folder 9)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Communist science drops conscience, Part I, 1959 Apr 7; UCLA Tape No. 117; 3-3/4 ips, full track. Lecture 6, Part I of II. (Box 92, Folder 10)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Communist science drops conscience, Part II, 1959 Apr 7; UCLA Tape No. 118; 3-3/4 ips, full track. Lecture 6, Part II of II. (Box 92, Folder 11)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, War and nationalism, Part I, 1959 Apr 13; UCLA Tape No. 119; 3-3/4 ips, full track. Lecture 7, Part I of II. (Box 92, Folder 12)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, War and nationalism, Part II, 1959 Apr 13; UCLA Tape No. 120; 3-3/4 ips, full track. Lecture 7, Part II of II. (Box 92, Folder 13)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, World's Future (The), Part I, 1959 Apr 20; UCLA Tape No. 121; 3-3/4 ips, full track. Lecture 8, Part I of II. (Box 92, Folder 14)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, World's Future (The), Part II, 1959 Apr 20; UCLA Tape No. 122; 3-3/4 ips, full track. Lecture 8, Part II of II. (Box 93, Folder 1)
      - Aldous Huxley, moderator, Darwin and Biology, 1959 Oct 23; UCLA Tape No. 123; 3-3/4 ips, full track. (Box 93, Folder 2)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Art, Artist, and Society, UCSB, 1959 Jun 1; UCLA Tape No. 124; 3-3/4 ips, full track. (Box 93, Folder 3)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Individual Life of Man (The), 1959 Sep 21; UCLA Tape No. 125; 3-3/4 ips, full track. Lecture 10. (Box 93, Folder 4)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Problem of Human Nature (The), 1959 Sep 28; UCLA Tape No. 126; 3-3/4 ips, full track. Lecture 11. (Box 93, Folder 5)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Ego (The), 1959 Oct 5; UCLA Tape No. 127; 3-3/4 ips, full track. Lecture 12. (Box 93, Folder 6)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Unconscious (the), 1959 Oct 12; UCLA Tape No. 128; 3-3/4 ips, full track. Lecture 13. (Box 93, Folder 7)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Language, 1959 Oct 26; UCLA Tape No. 129; 3-3/4 ips, full track. Lecture 14. (Box 93, Folder 8)
      - Aldous Huxley, moderator, Darwin and Social Sciences, 1959 Nov 6; UCLA Tape No. 130; 3-3/4 ips, full track. (Box 93, Folder 9)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Art, 1959 Nov 9; UCLA Tape No. 131; 3-3/4 ips, full track. Lecture 15. (Box 93, Folder 10)
      - Aldous Huxley, moderator, Darwin and Religion, 1959 Nov 20; UCLA Tape No. 132; 3-3/4 ips, full track. (Box 93, Folder 11)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Man and Religion, 1959 Nov 23; UCLA Tape No. 133; 3-3/4 ips, full track. Lecture 16. (Box 93, Folder 12)
      - Aldous Huxley, moderator, Darwin and Philosophy, 1959 Dec 4; UCLA Tape No. 134; 3-3/4 ips, full track. (Box 93, Folder 13)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Latent Human Potentialities, Part I, 1959 Dec 7; UCLA Tape No. 135; 3-3/4 ips, full track. Lecture 17, Part I of II. (Box 93, Folder 14)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Latent Human Potentialities, Part II (original tape damaged), 1959 Dec 7; UCLA Tape No. 136; 3-3/4 ips, full track. Lecture 17, Part II of II. (Box 93, Folder 15)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Natural History of Visions, Part I, UCSB, 1959 Dec 14; UCLA Tape No. 137; 3-3/4 ips, full track. Part I of II. (Box 93, Folder 16)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Human potentialities, conclusion (continued from UCLA tape no. 142A); Aldous Huxley, interview, "Kaleidoscope", NET-TV, 1962 Oct; 1963 Jul 21; UCLA Tape No. 142B; See 142 (Box 94)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Visionary Experience, Part II (continued from 147A), Discussion with students (low sound quality), Lake Forest College, Lake Forest, IL., 1960 Apr 7; UCLA Tape No. 147B; See 147 (Box 94)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Visionary Experience, Part I, Lake Forest College, Lake Forest, IL., 1960 Apr 7; UCLA Tape No. 147A; See 147 (Box 94)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Human potentialities (concluded on UCLA tape no. 142B), 1962 Oct; UCLA Tape No. 142A; See 142 (Box 94)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Natural history of visions, Part II, UCSB, 1959 Dec 14; UCLA Tape No. 138; 3-3/4 ips, full track. Part II of II. (Box 94, Folder 1)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Man and civilization: Control of the mind, Part I, UC Berkeley, 1961 Jan 28; UCLA Tape No. 139; 3-3/4 ips, full track. U.C. Berkeley. Part I. (Box 94, Folder 2)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Man and civilization: Control of the mind, Part II, UC Berkeley, 1961 Jan 28; UCLA Tape No. 140; 3-3/4 ips, full track. U.C. Berkeley. Part II. (Box 94, Folder 3)
      - Aldous Huxley and others, panel and discussion, Politics of Ecology, Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions, Santa Barbara, CA, 1962 Mar; UCLA Tape No. 141; 3-3/4 ips, half track. U.C. Berkeley. Part II. Approx. 48 minutes. Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions. (Box 94, Folder 4)
      - 142A: Aldous Huxley, lecture, Human potentialities; 142B: Aldous Huxley, interview, "Kaleidoscope", NET- TV, 1962 Oct; 1963 Jul 21; UCLA Tape No. 142; 3-3/4 ips, one each side. Side 1: Aldous Huxley speaking on "Human potentialities," taped at Shimer College, Mount Carroll, Illinois. Original owned by radio station WNIB-FM, Chicaglo, Ill. Duplicate of M. Sullivan's H-5. Side 2: Conclusion of above and then interview with Aldous Huxley on NET-TV program, "Kaleidoscope." Re-run on WTTV, Chicago, original date not known. Duplicate of M. Sullivan's H-6. (Box 94, Folder 5)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Matter, mind and the question of survival, Part II, UCSB, 1960 May 10; UCLA Tape No. 144 (Box 94, Folder 7)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Matter, mind and the question of survival, Part I, UCSB, 1960 May 10; UCLA Tape No. 145 (Box 94, Folder 8)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Visionary Experience, Lake Forest College, Lake Forest, IL., 1960 Apr 7; UCLA Tape No. 147; 3-34 ips, 1 each side, monophonic. Taped at Lake Forest College, Lake Forest, Ill. Completed on side 2, and followed by discussion with students next day. Duplicate from original owned by Lake Forest College, Sullivan's H-2. (Box 94, Folder 10)
      - Symposium on the Control of the Mind, Opening remarks and introduction, UC San Francisco, 1961; UCLA Tape No. 148; S.F. symposium on drugs, chairman introducing A. (Box 94, Folder 11)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Who are We?: Contemporary ideas, psychological aspects, Lecture IV, Part I, 1960 Apr 11; UCLA Tape No. 161A; See 161 (Box 95)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Who are We?: Human potentialities, Lecture VI, Part II (continued from 163A), 1960 Apr 25; UCLA Tape No. 163B; See 163 (Box 95)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Who are We?: Human potentialities, Lecture VI, Part I, 1960 Apr 25; UCLA Tape No. 163A; See 163 (Box 95)
      - Aldous Huxley, Panel discussion, Ultimate revolution (The)Part I, Berkeley Language Center [?], 1962 Mar 20; UCLA Tape No. 157A; See 157 (Box 95)
      - Aldous Huxley, Panel discussion, Ultimate revolution (The) Part II (continued from 157A), Question and answer session, Berkeley Language Center [?], 1962 Mar 20; UCLA Tape No. 157B; See 157 (Box 95)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Who are We?: Contemporary ideas, psychological aspects, Lecture IV, Part II (continued from 161A), 1960 Apr 11; UCLA Tape No. 161B; See 161 (Box 95)
      - Aldous Huxley, Control of the Mind Symposium: Human potentialities, University of California, Rebroadcast on "Voices of Reason", Canadian Broadcasting Corporation, 1966 Sep 9; UCLA Tape No. 156; Note on reel label: "Voices of reason dub, Sept. 9*66, 01618." (Box 95, Folder 5)
      - Aldous Huxley, Panel discussion, Ultimate revolution (The), Berkeley Language Center [?], 1962 Mar 20; UCLA Tape No. 157; Note on reel label: "Huxley, A. 'The ultimate revolution,' 20/3/62." (Box 95, Folder 6)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Who are We?: Ancient concepts of human nature, Lecture I, 1960 Mar 28; UCLA Tape No. 158; Note on reel label: "Who are we? #10, 1960." (Box 95, Folder 7)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Who are We?: Contemporary ideas, Lecture II, 1960 Apr 4; UCLA Tape No. 159; Note on reel label: "Who are we? #11, 1960." (Box 95, Folder 8)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Who are We?: Symbols & first order experiences, Lecture III, 1960 Apr 6; UCLA Tape No. 160; Note on reel label: "Who are we? #12, 1960." (Box 95, Folder 9)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Who are We?: Contemporary ideas, psychological aspects, Lecture IV, 1960 Apr 11; UCLA Tape No. 161; Note on reel label: "Who are we? #13, 1960." (Box 95, Folder 10)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Who are We?: The individual in history, Lecture V, 1960 Apr 18; UCLA Tape No. 162; Note on reel label: "Who are we? #14, 1960." (Box 95, Folder 11)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Who are We?: Human potentialities, Lecture VI, 1960 Apr 25; UCLA Tape No. 163; Note on reel label: "Who are we? #15, 1960." (Box 95, Folder 12)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Human Potentialities [?], unknown location, Part I, no date; UCLA Tape No. 164; Huxley #1 (Box 95, Folder 13)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Human Potentialities [?], unknown location, Part II, no date; UCLA Tape No. 165; Huxley #2 (Box 95, Folder 14)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, What a piece of work is a man?, Ancient Views of Human Nature, Lecture I, MIT, NAEB Radio Network, 1960 Sep; UCLA Tape No. 166; With notes on back of box: "Huxley, Aldous. What a piece of work is a man? 3-3/4. Producer: T.M. For Harper's - Beaulah Hagen. To: Iden Scott. Reel 1 of 7. Dub." (Box 96, Folder 1)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, What a piece of work is a man?, Contemporary Picture (The), Lecture II, MIT, NAEB Radio Network, 1960; UCLA Tape No. 167; With notes on back of box: "Huxley, Aldous. What a piece of work is a man? 3-3/4. For Harper's - Beaulah Hagen. To: Iden Scott. Reel 2 of 7. Dub." (Box 96, Folder 2)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, What a piece of work is a man?, Individual in History (The), Lecture III, MIT, NAEB Radio Network, 1964 Mar 7; UCLA Tape No. 168; With notes on back of box: "Huxley, Aldous. What a piece of work is a man? 3-3/4. dubbed March 7, 1964. By HBM. AMPEX. Note: Tail out!!!! Rewind before playing. To: Scott for Harper & Row. Reel 3 of 7." (Box 96, Folder 3)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, What a piece of work is a man?, Symbols and Immediate Experience, Lecture IV, MIT, NAEB Radio Network, 1964 Mar 7; UCLA Tape No. 169; With notes on back of box: "Huxley, Aldous. What a piece of work is a man? 3-3/4. dubbed March 7, 1964. By HBM. AMPEX. Full. Note: Tail out!!!! Rewind before playing. To: Scott for Harper & Row. Reel 4 of 7. Dub." (Box 96, Folder 4)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, What a piece of work is a man?, Why Art?, Lecture V, MIT, NAEB Radio Network, 1964 Mar 7; UCLA Tape No. 170; With notes on back of box: "Huxley, Aldous. What a piece of work is a man? 1960. 3-3/4. dubbed March 7, 1964. By HBM. AMPEX. Full. Note: Tail out!!!! Rewind before playing. To: Scott for Harper & Row. Reel 5 of 7. Dub." (Box 96, Folder 5)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, What a piece of work is a man?, Visionary Experience, Lecture VI, MIT, NAEB Radio Network, 1964 Mar 7; UCLA Tape No. 171; With notes on back of box: "Huxley, Aldous. What a piece of work is a man? 1960. #6. 3-3/4. dubbed March 7, 1964. By HBM. AMPEX. Full. Note: Tail out!!!! Rewind before playing. To: Scott for Harper & Row. Reel 6 of 7. Dub. Note: This tape has broken in the middle. " (Box 96, Folder 6)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, What a piece of work is a man?, Human Potentialities, Lecture VII, MIT, NAEB Radio Network, 1964 Mar 7; UCLA Tape No. 172; With notes on back of box: "Huxley, Aldous. What a piece of work is a man? 1960. #6 [sic]. 3-3/4. dubbed March 7, 1964. By HBM. AMPEX. Full. Note: Tail out!!!! Rewind before playing. To: Scott for Harper & Row. Reel 7 of 7. Dub. Note: This tape has broken in the middle. " (Box 96, Folder 7)
      - Duplicate of UCLA Tape no. 166, Aldous Huxley, What a piece of work is a man?, Ancient Views of Human Nature, Lecture I, MIT, no date; UCLA Tape No. 173; Variant of sound quality (Box 96, Folder 8)
      - Duplicate of UCLA Tape no. 167, Aldous Huxley, lecture, What a piece of work is a man?, Contemporary Picture (The), Lecture II, MIT, no date; UCLA Tape No. 174 (Box 96, Folder 9)
      - Duplicate of UCLA Tape no. 168, Aldous Huxley, lecture, What a piece of work is a man?, Individual in History (The), Part III, MIT, no date; UCLA Tape No. 175 (Box 96, Folder 10)
      - Duplicate of UCLA Tape no. 169, Aldous Huxley, lecture, What a piece of work is a man?, Symbols and Immediate Experience, Lecture IV, MIT, no date; UCLA Tape No. 176 (Box 96, Folder 11)
      - Duplicate of UCLA Tape no. 170, Aldous Huxley, lecture, What a piece of work is a man?, Why Art?, Lecture V, MIT, no date; UCLA Tape No. 177 (Box 96, Folder 12)
      - Duplicate of UCLA Tape no. 171, Aldous Huxley, lecture, What a piece of work is a man?, Visionary Experience, Lecture VI, MIT, 1960 Nov 9; UCLA Tape No. 178; Note on box: "Huxley lecture #6, Visionary experience, Part I, Part II (2nd side), sent by Roy Lawson, MIT, 3 Feb 65" (Box 96, Folder 13)
      - Duplicate of UCLA Tape no. 172, Aldous Huxley, lecture, What a piece of work is a man?, Human Potentialities, Lecture VII, MIT, no date; UCLA Tape No. 179; Note on box: "Human potentials" (Box 96, Folder 14)
      - Aldous Huxley, narrator, dramatization of Brave New World, The Theater of the Mind, CBS radio, 1956; UCLA Tape No. 181A; See 181 (Box 97)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Visionary Experience (continued from 181 A, originally 2nd half of UCLA tape no. 181), no date; UCLA Tape No. 181B; See 181 (Box 97)
      - Duplicate of UCLA Tape no. 190 Aldous Huxley, lecture, Possibilities of man (The), San Francisco State College, 1961 Dec 7; UCLA Tape No. 191A; See 191 (Box 97)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Visionary Experience, UC Berkeley, 1962 Apr 24; UCLA Tape No. 191B; See 191 (Box 97)
      - Aldous Huxley, narrator, dramatization of Brave New World, The Theater of the Mind, CBS radio; Aldous Huxley, lecture, Visionary Experience, 1956; no date; UCLA Tape No. 181; Narrated by AH. CBS radio workshop. William Conrad. (Box 97, Folder 2)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Why Art? (poor recording quality), 1960 Apr; UCLA Tape No. 182; Note on box: "3-3/4 ips. A. Tape from Lynch." (Box 97, Folder 3)
      - Aldous Huxley with Lawrence Clark Powell, Majl Ewing, Grover Jacoby, Mrs. Frieda Lawrence Ravagli, Mrs. D. Mitchell, D.H. Lawrence roundtable, Friends of the Library (recording continued on UCLA tape no. 184), 1952 Mar 7; UCLA Tape No. 183; Reel #1. (Box 97, Folder 4)
      - Aldous Huxley with Lawrence Clark Powell, Majl Ewing, Grover Jacoby, Mrs. Frieda Lawrence Ravagli, Mrs. D. Mitchell, D.H. Lawrence roundtable, Friends of the Library (continued from UCLA tape no. 183), 1952 Mar 7; UCLA Tape No. 184; Reel #2. (Box 97, Folder 5)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Human Potentialities, MIT (poor sound quality), 1960 Apr; UCLA Tape No. 185; Note on box: "3-3/4 ips. A tape from Lynch." (Box 97, Folder 6)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Visionary Experience, unknown location (poor sound quality), 1960; UCLA Tape No. 186; Note on box: "3-3/4"(?), ink is faded. (Box 97, Folder 7)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Human Potentialities, Symposium on the Control of the Mind, UC San Francisco, 1961 Jan 28; UCLA Tape No. 187; 3-3/4 speed. Note on box: "Track I. A-296. Human potentialities. Aldous Huxley. L-64'00". Intro-16'20". Closing- 0' 55". Jan 28, 1961. Track 2, cont. Un. Of Cal. San Francisco symposium on The Control of the Mind." (Box 97, Folder 8)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Population Explosion of World and Its Consequences, unknown location, 1960 Sep 9; UCLA Tape No. 188; Note on box: "H-9: Dartmouth College Convocation, "Great Issues of Conscience in Modern Medicine", Sept. 9, 1960, Chairman: Rene J. Dobos introduces Aldous Huxley, not titled, but about "Population explosion of world & its consequences," monoral, 1 hour @ 3-34 ips: dupe from Dartmouth. For Mrs. Aldous Huxley from Mercer Sullivan." (Box 97, Folder 9)
      - Aldous Huxley, narrator, opening remarks only, dramatization of Brave New World, The Theater of the Mind, CBS radio, no date; UCLA Tape No. 189; Reel 1 - 4" tape. Reel 2 - 3" tape. Reel 3 - 4" tape. (Box 97, Folder 10)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Possibilities of man (The), San Francisco State College, 1961 Dec 7; UCLA Tape No. 190; Note on box: "Aldous Huxley, "The Possibilities of Man," San Francisco State College." (Box 97, Folder 11)
      - Duplicate of UCLA Tape no. 190, Aldous Huxley, lecture, Possibilities of man (The), San Francisco State College; Aldous Huxley, lecture, Visionary experience, UC Berkeley, 1961 Dec 7; 1962 Apr 24; UCLA Tape No. 191; Note on box: " two track recording, 3-3/4 ips. Track one: Aldous Huxley, "The Possibilities of Man," San Francisco State College, Dec. 7, 1961, intro. 3" 20", lecture 54" 45". Track two: aldous Huxley, "Visionary Experience, U.C. Berkeley, April 24, 1962, intorduction by E.W. Strong, intro. 12" 05", lecture: 32" 42". Box label is from University of California, Berkeley, Language Laboratory." (Box 97, Folder 12)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Visionary Experience, unknown location, no date; UCLA Tape No. 192; 3-3/4. Note on box: "Dub of tape as edited on record - Visionary experience." (Box 97, Folder 13)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Visionary Experience, unknown location (different from UCLA Tape no. 192), 1962 Apr 24; UCLA Tape No. 193; 3-3/4. Note on box: "Track 1, A-176, Visionary expereicne, Aldous Huxley, L-32' 45", Q 0 12' 05", closing - 2' 00", April 24, 1962." (Box 97, Folder 14)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Human Potentialities, symposium [?] [rebroadcast?], 1965 Apr 1; UCLA Tape No. 200A; See 200 (Box 98)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Human Potentialities, symposium [?] [rebroadcast?] (continued from UCLA Tape no. 200 A), 1965 Apr 1; UCLA Tape No. 200B; See 200 (Box 98)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Human Potentialities, symposium ?, 1965 Apr 1; UCLA Tape No. 200; Note on box: "Reel 1, 3/3/4 tape speed, date 4-1-65, Master, 80 minutes, Aldous Huxley, 1-1/2 sides, Human potentialities." (Box 98, Folder 6)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Visionary Experience, Colgate (?) Symposium, Hamilton, NY, April 1962; UCLA Tape No. 201; Note on box: "Reel 1, 3/3/4 tape speed, date 4-1-65, Master, 80 minutes, Aldous Huxley, 1-1/2 sides, Visionary experience,Berkeley, 1) Bach, 2 Intro, 3 ) Aldous - Visionary experience, Colgate (?) Symposium, Hamilton, NY - April 1962." (Box 98, Folder 7)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Visionary experience, unknown location, Part II ?, no date; UCLA Tape No. 202; Note on tape label: "Huxley - Visionary experience - 15 ips Master." (Box 98, Folder 8)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Visionary experience, unknown location, Part I ?, no date; UCLA Tape No. 203; Note on tape label: "Huxley - Visionary experience - 15 ips Master." Note on box: "Ellen Gifford." (Box 98, Folder 9)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Visionary experience, unknown location, Part IV?, no date; UCLA Tape No. 204; Note on tape label: "Huxley - Visionary experience - 15 ips Master." (Box 98, Folder 10)
      - Duplicate of UCLA Tape no. 203, Aldous Huxley, Visionary experience, unknown location, Part I ?, no date; UCLA Tape No. 205; Note on box: "3-3/4 ips full track, Aldous Huxley, Visionary experience (edited for LP)." (Box 98, Folder 11)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, Human Potentialities, no date; UCLA Tape No. 206; Note on box: "Aldous Huxley: Human potentialities, copy of redited record master, 3-3/4 ips monophonic copy, heads." (Box 98, Folder 12)
      - Aldous Huxley, narrator, dramatization of Brave New World, Theater of the Mind, CBS Radio Workshop, 1956; UCLA Tape No. 215; Note on insert: "Brave New World, CBS Radio Workshop 1.27.56, 2.3.56, Aldous Speaking" (Box 99, Folder 5)
      - Julian Huxley, The Evolutionary Vision, Darwin Centennial Celebration, 1959; UCLA Tape No. 216; Note on insert: "The Chicago Centennial" MS. Note attached: "The Chicago Darwin Centennial, 1959, A-, Julian and others" (Box 99, Folder 6)
      - Aldous Huxley, lecture, The Ultimate Revolution [?], KPFA, rebroadcast?, 1959; UCLA Tape No. 217; Note on insert: "The Ultimate Revolution; Not clear" (Box 99, Folder 7)
      - Aldous Huxley, moderator, Whither Evolution: The Darwin Centennial, KPFA, 1960; UCLA Tape No. 219 (Box 99, Folder 9)
      - Laura Huxley and William Irwin Thompson, panelists, Children: Our Ultimate Investment [?], 1994; UCLA Tape No. 227; Handwritten label reads: "194 Conference Questions and Answers," Recording ends abruptly (Box 100, Folder 5)
      - Label reads: "Aldous Huxley Human Potentialities AH-1-768A/B 15ips half-track mono MASTER", no date; UCLA Tape No. 423; not digitized; large reel 15 ips (Box 107, Folder 1)